MAFC - Information

Make a Fun Chapter is a contest which goes exactly as it sounds: the goal is to make a fun chapter.
This contest has seen three entries, from General Ciraxis, Aura Wolf, and GhastStation respectively.

GhastStation's entry is not included in the public pack because it is the prologue of his personal project,
FE: Bloodlines, and he has asked for it not to be distributed because he intends on releasing a demo of the
project soon anyway. This is the first and last time that someone is just ripping a chapter from their hack to
submit to this: if there are any more of these contests, there will be a rule that you cannot just lift a chapter
from your hack to submit and the submission has to be able to stand on its own.
The two entries that are included both patch to FE7.

The objective of MAFC is to inspire interest in Fire Emblem modding at TEB and also to inspire people
to make stuff— so often folk get bogged down by planning or a huge personal project or whatever that they
never release anything. However, it is important to put out material and get critique on it and improve, so here
we are.

The judges of the contest this time are Sqawl, MarkyJoe, and Robbel. They will play through each entry
and decide on a winner.

There's nothing more to say— hope you have fun!