
To patch successfully, you will need NUPs and a FE7 (U) ROM.
-> "Apply an UPS patch to a file"
-> Select the ROM and one of the two .UPS patches.
-> Select "Ignore"
-> Select "Patch"

You should know be able to try out this project. Have fun!



Credits

Head of the Chapter
Aura Wolf

Special Thanks To
Thorbjørn Lindeijer- Author of Tiled. While I generally don't use Tiled, it looks ideal for tile changes.
Robin Burrows- Author of Mappy. Thanks for the amazing map editor!
Nintenlord- Made the .MAR array inserter (Yes, I inserted one of the maps through Mappy), the Tiled Map inserter, Event Assembler, and EAstdlib.
Probably did more as well.
Creator of Nightmare and its numerous modules- Most people wouldn't want to change stats, pointers, etc., in a hex editor, and that includes me.
Thanks!
Arch- For his amazing tutorial on event construction.
Markyjoe- For his Tiled tutorial, map pointer charts, and his advice on great gameplay.
Blazer- For the Ultimate Tutorial. It especially helped with learning ASM, so thanks!
Xeld/Hextator/whateverhegoesby- For FEditor. Text editing is a lot easier through this than Anti-Huffman and Parsing (iirc those were the old methods,
it's been years since I last did Anti-Huffman).
Brendor- For his findings on changing the default options in a hex editor, as well as his Set Gold ASM.
Shadowofchaos- For the Start on Eliwood Mode Without Tactician patch.
Cedar- For Eventiel, though I primarily use it for whenever I focus the camera to a location. Also an important part of the TEB community.
TEB- For being an amazing community.
Anyone that I forgot and that should be credited (or feels they should).
You, for playing (Hopefully...!)



Version History

V0.8
Early release for gameplay feedback (primarily)

V1.0
Fixed death quotes and other issues
Added Post-Gameplay